얘들아
이걸 봐, 믿지 못할 거야
Hey! You're not gonna believe this.
물론 여자 알몸이 실린
잡지도 세상에 돌아다녀
Yes, Ross, we know they have magazines
with pictures of naked women in them.
오! 비디오 얘기도 해줘라
Don't tell him about the videos!
I made up a joke
and sent it in to Playboy.
내가 지어낸 조크를
플레이보이에 보냈는데
They printed it.
그게 실렸어
플레이보이에 조크도 실려?
I didn't know they print jokes.
그럼, 조크는 물론
They print jokes, interviews,
hard-hitting journalism.
인터뷰, 이슈가 되는 기사
누드사진만 실리는 게 아냐
It's not just about the pictures.
엄마한테 안 통하는 거면
우리한테도 안 통해
Didn't work on Mom,
it's not gonna work on us.
여기야, 봐
처음에 나와
Check it out. It's the first one.
Right there.
That is funny.
정말 재미있다
내가 지어낼 때도 웃겼어
It was also funny when I made it up.
- 뭐?
- 내가 지어낸 조크야
-What?
-I made that joke up.
아냐, 내가 지어냈어
No, you didn't. I did.
무슨 말씀, 회사에서 댄한테
써먹었더니 최고의 조크라더라
Yes, I did. I told Dan and he said it
was the funniest joke he'd ever heard.
댄한테 고맙다고 전해 줘
Hey, tell Dan thanks.
What?
왜?
미안, 그 밑에 있는 거
이거 진짜 웃긴다
I was just reading the joke below it.
Man, that one is funny.
Monica, you remember me
telling you that joke, right?
모니카, 내가 자기한테
이 얘기해줬잖아
-No.
-Seriously?
- 아니
- 잘 생각해봐
네 조크가 한두 개니?
You tell a lot of jokes.
챈들러, 내가 만든 거야
Look, it's my joke.
But if it makes you feel better,
they don't print the name.
위로가 될 진 모르지만
이름은 안 실리니까
누구 거든 상관없잖아?
So it doesn't really matter
who gets credit.
그래
Yeah, I guess.
얘들아
-Hey, guys.
-Playboy printed my joke!
조이, 내 조크가
플레이보이에 실렸어
아냐, 내 거야
전화해서 확인해봐
No, it's mine! Call them!
They'll tell you!
-My joke!
- 내 조크야
- 내 거라니까
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
조크라니
Jokes? What...?
거기 알몸 여자들
실리는 거 알기나 해?
You know there's naked chicks
in there, right?
The One With The Joke
Dude! You have got to turn on
Behind The Music.
야, '추억의 음악캠프' 좀 봐라
그룹 'Heart'가 아무래도
해체될 위기에 처했나 봐
The band Heart is having a tough
time and they may break up.
그럼 너희 집 가서 보자
Let's watch that at your place.
안 돼, 모니카가
요리 채널 보고 있어
Monica's watching a show. I don't
want to miss when they were skinny.
빨리, 걔들 살찌기 전에
봐두고 싶어
Hey, Chandler?
You know what we should do?
야, 챈들러
이럴 게 아니라
우리 나가서 선글라스
하나씩 사자
You and I should go out
and get some new sunglasses.
뭐? 싫어
난 이거 볼래
What? No, I want to watch this.
케이블 나갔냐?
-Did your cable go out?
-No. No, that's VH1.
아니, VH1이잖아
요즘 애들 듣는 음악은
완전히 소음 아니냐
I tell you, the music
these kids listen to today...
it's a lot of noise to me.
Why is your cable out?
케이블이 왜 안 나오지?
그러고 보니까
시청료를 안 냈다
Oh, because I haven't really
paid the bill.
내가 돈 꿔준다니까
왜 고집을 부려
If you need money,
would you please let me loan you some?
싫어, 됐다니까 그러네
No, Chandler. Forget about it, okay?
재닌이 나가는 통에
좀 힘든 건 사실이야
I know things have been tight since
Janine moved out. God, was she hot.
끝내주는 애였지
안다
I know, yeah.
뭐 죽기야 하겠냐?
Look, I can handle it, all right?
I can listen to the radio.
라디오 들으면 돼
로스가 이 쌈빡한 책도 줬어
And Ross gave me this great book.
알았다, 조크 도둑놈 집에서
TV 봐도 되는지 물어보자
Want to see if the joke stealer
will let us watch at his place?
그래
Sure.
- 전화요금은 냈냐?
- 냈을 턱이 있나
-Paid your phone bill?
-No.
얘들아
너였구나
It's only you.
뭐하는 거야?
-What are you doing?
-Looking at a Playboy.
플레이보이 본다
나도 볼래
I want to look too!
오호라!
Yikes!
이 사진에 무슨
스토리가 있을까?
Do you think these pictures
are trying to tell a story?
그럼
Sure. Like in the case
of this young woman...
이 아가씨의 경우는
옷을 잃어버린 모양이야
she has lost her clothes.
알몸으로 말을 타며 이렇게
외치는 거지, '내 옷! 내 옷! '
So she rides naked on the horse,
she's crying out, "Where are they?"
풀밭에 발라당 누워서
옷은 어떻게 찾는대?
She's not gonna find them,
lying in the grass like that.
헛간에서 셔츠 걷어올리고
허리 숙이던 거 기억나니?
Remember the days when you'd
go out to the barn...
Lift up your shirt and bend over?
그럼
이 여자랑 사귀고 싶다
You see, now, I would date this girl.
귀엽고, 자연을 좋아하고
She's cute, she's outdoorsy.
불도 잘 지필 걸?
쓸모가 많잖아
And she knows how to build a fire.
That'll come in handy.
하나 물어보자
I got a question.
우리 중 한 명이랑 사귄다면
넌 누굴 선택할래?
If you had to pick one of us to date,
who would it be?
모르겠어
-I don't know.
-Me neither.
나도 몰라
Rachel.
레이첼
What?
뭐?
모르겠어
I don't know.
나도 몰라
Me neither.
You know, you forget how many
great songs Heart had.
'Heart'가 수많은 명곡을
발표한 거 알지?
그럼
키보드로 맨 먼저
연주한 게 'Barracuda'였어
"Barracuda" was the first song
I learned to play on the keyboard.
듣고 반복해서 따라하면
So you heard it, you repeated it...
네 작품이 된다 이거지?
so that must mean you wrote it.
야, 그만들 해라
솔직히 말하면
You guys with this joke.
Well, I gotta say...
나도 웃긴 했지만
아직 이해가 안 돼
I know I cracked up,
but I'm not even sure I got it.
뭐?
What?
이해가 안 돼?
You didn't get it?
의사가 원숭이라니까
The doctor is a monkey.
And monkeys
can't write out prescriptions.
원숭이는 처방전을 못 써
그렇지
누가 내 조크 듣고 웃으래!
You are not allowed
to laugh at my joke.
Your joke?
네 조크?
그쪽 생각은 좀 다르던 걸?
Well, I think the Hef
would disagree.
나한테 100달러짜리
수표를 보내왔거든
Which is why he sent me a check...
for $100.
내 조크 훔친 것도 모자라
내 돈까지 훔쳤구만
So you stole my joke
and you stole my money?
현금출납기에 넣으려 했는데
I was gonna stick it in the ATM.
이젠 섹시한 은행직원한테 내가
유명작가란 사실을 알리고 싶어
But now I think I'll show
the sexy teller...
that I am a published writer.
조크 도둑이란 사실을
알게 될 거다
She'll know that you stole the joke.
뭘 어쩌겠다고
날 따라오시게?
You gonna follow me there?
그래
-Yeah.
-I'm not gonna go now.
- 그럼 안 갈란다
- 좋으실 대로
Okay.
Here you go.
여기
건터?
Gunther?
난 못 내겠어요
I can't pay now,
because I'm not working.
백수 주제에 흥청망청
쓰고 살 순 없죠
I've had to cut down
on some luxuries like...
이건 도로 물릴게요
paying for stuff, so....
괜찮다면 여기서 일해
Well, if you want, you can work here.
글쎄요, 저기 그게...
I don't know.
It's just....
내가 드라마에
고정 출연했던 거 알죠?
See, I was a regular on a soap opera,
you know?
체면이라는 것도 있고...
And to go from that to this,
it's just....
게다가 친구들도 자주 오는데
And plus, I'd have to wait
on all my friends.
돈이 싫다면 할 수 없고
Okay. But the money's good.
Plus, you get to stare at Rachel
as much as you want.
여기 있으면 종일
레이첼도 볼 수 있는데
네?
What?
근무시간은 자유라고
Flexible hours.
Maybe I could be a waiter.
못할 것도 없죠 뭐
전화 좀 쓸까요?
Could I use the phone?
피비는 레이첼을 택했어
She picked Rachel.
나중에 부인했지만
분명 레이첼이었다고
She tried to back out of it, but
it was obvious. She picked Rachel.
감히 내 조크를 훔치다니
He took my joke. He just took it.
그건 나쁜 짓이지
이것도 나빠
This is wrong.
You know what else is wrong?
피비가 레이첼을 택한 거
Phoebe picking Rachel.
레이첼 택한 사람 또 있어
Know who else picked Rachel? Ross.
로스야, 그것도 부족해서
내 조크까지 훔쳤어
Know what else Ross did?
He stole my joke.
이제 조크 일지를 쓸 거야
I'm gonna get a joke journal,
you know?
내 조크의 날짜와 시간을
모두 기록해두겠어
And document the date and time
of every single one of my jokes.
- 좋은 생각이다
- 그래
Good idea. Know what's a bad idea?
- 나쁜 생각은 뭔지 알아?
- 레이첼 찍은 거
-Picking Rachel.
-That's right.
당연하지
Did you hear something?
무슨 소리 들었어?
Maybe it's the sound of Ross climbing
into my brain to steal my thoughts.
내 생각을 훔치러 머릿속으로
기어 들어오는 로스 소리겠지
거실에서 난다
It's coming from the living room.
책은 다 읽었거든
I finished my book.
- 안녕, 얘들아
- 어서 와
-Hey, you guys.
-Hey.
너희들 잘 어울린다
Don't you guys look cute.
참 귀여운 한 쌍이야
You guys make a cute couple.
이게 무슨 소리지?
What are you doing?
Just trying to re-create some of
the fun that we had at my place.
아냐, 전에 우리 집에서 했던
놀이가 너무 재미있어서
나 말고 레이첼을 선택한 거
Remember? When you picked
Rachel over me?
That was funny.
진짜 웃기더라
그래, 좀 웃겼어
-It was kind of funny.
-It wasn't funny at all!
웃기기도 하겠다
왜 그랬어?
Why would you do that?
왜 날 안 골랐지?
Why didn't you pick me?
좋아
Fine.
내가 너보다 레이첼한테
약간 더 기울었던 이유는...
The reason I was leaning a little
bit more toward Rachel than you...
is just, you know, you're...
넌 결벽증이 좀 있잖아
점심이나 먹으러 가자
high maintenance.
Let's go to lunch!
That is completely untrue.
그건 말도 안 돼
You think I'm high maintenance?
Prove it.
내가 결벽증이라고?
그럼 증명해봐, 리스트
만들어서 조목조목 따지자
You write out a list, and
we'll go through it point by point.
No, you're right, you're easygoing.
그래, 맞다
너도 참 편해
레이첼만큼 편하진 않지만
You're just not as easygoing
as Rachel. She's just more...
쟨 너보다 나긋나긋하고
부드러워, 그게 다야
flexible and mellow. That's all.
사람이 다 같을 순 없지
Well, people are different.
레이첼은 시키는 대로 다 해
자근자근 밟아도 괜찮아
Rachel will do whatever you want.
You can just walk all over her.
뭐? 사람을 뭘로 보고
내가 만만한 호구야?
What? Are you saying that I'm
a pushover? I'm not a pushover.
그래, 너 호구 아니다
Oh, okay. You're not a pushover.
지금 호구라고 생각하잖아
You think I'm a pushover.
Well, watch this.
잘 들어, 나 너랑
점심 안 먹어
You're not invited to lunch!
What do you think?
Pretty strong, I think.
나도 한다면 하는 사람이야
모니카, 점심 먹으러 가자
Come on, Monica, let's go to lunch.
리스트나 작성해둬
You start working on that list.
- 기가 막혀서
- 누가 아니래
-I cannot believe her.
-I know. Where do you want to eat?
뭘 먹을까?
오! 그 일식집 죽이더라
-Oh, I love that Japanese place.
-I'm sick of Japanese. Not there.
난 일식 진저리난다
- 그럼 너 좋은 대로 가자
- 그래
Wherever you want to go is cool.
Oh, hey, Gunther...
건터, 이것 좀 볼래요?
check this out.
아까 챈들러한테 들었어
Yeah, that Chandler cracks me up.
야, 로스
You want anything to drink?
I'm heading up there.
뭐 마실래?
가는 길이니까
그래, 난 커피
고맙다
-I'll take a coffee. Thanks.
-Sure.
뭘
-Coffee?
-No.
- 커피?
- 됐어
커피 줄까?
내가 다녀오는 김에
Coffee? I'm going up there.
- 아니, 됐어
- 그래
No, thank you.
필요한 거 있으세요?
제가 가려던 참이라
You need anything?
I'm heading up there.
- 얼음물 한 잔 부탁해요
- 좋습니다
I'd love ice water.
You got it.
조이, 너 뭐해?
What are you doing?
봉사 좀 하려고
Just being friendly.
조이, 너 거기
들어가면 안 되잖아
You're not supposed to go back there.
아냐, 괜찮아
그렇죠, 건터?
It's okay. Right?
윙크하지 마
Don't wink at me.
And put on your apron.
앞치마나 두르고
Okay.
좋아요
앞치마 두르는 손님도
내가 처음일 거야
I don't see you asking other
paying customers to put on aprons.
-Joey, do you work here?
-No.
조이, 너 여기서 일하니?
아니
- 웨이터?
- 넵!
-Waiter.
-Yeah!
조이, 무슨 일이야?
왜 우리한테 얘기 안 했어?
What's going on?
Why didn't you tell us you work here?
창피하잖아
It's kind of embarrassing. I mean,
I was an actor, now I'm a waiter.
배우 생활하다 웨이터라니
그 반대로 가야지
It's supposed to go
the other direction.
So's your apron.
You're wearing it like a cape.
앞치마도 뒤집혔다
그거 망토 아냐
I mean, the job's easy
and the money's good, you know?
힘든 일도 아니고
보수도 괜찮아
I guess if I'm hanging out here,
I might as well get paid for it.
어차피 여기서 살다시피 하는데
돈 받고 하는 게 낫지
I just feel kind of weird
serving you guys, you know?
너희한테 주문 받는 게
좀 이상하지만
It'll be great.
무슨 소리야
조이, 나도 해봤지만 괜찮아
Come on, I did it and it was fine.
그래, 이상할 게 뭐 있어
Why would it be weird?
Hey, Joey? Can I get some coffee?
야, 조이
나 커피 한 잔 마실까?
It doesn't seem that weird.
그래, 듣고 보니
이상하지도 않네
I asked before.
You still haven't gotten it.
그게 아니라 아까 주문한 거
아직도 안 나왔잖아
또 이상해졌어
See, now it's weird again.
You're gonna make a lot of money.
Here's your first tip.
여기 있으면 돈도 꽤 벌 거야
내가 첫 번째 충고를 해주지
Don't eat yellow snow.
옐로스노는 먹지 말 것
2시 15분, 커피하우스!
2:15, coffeehouse.
잘됐다, 드디어 내 노하우를
전수할 사람이 생겼어
This is great. Finally,
someone I can pass my wisdom to.
내가 여기 있으면서
배운 게 좀 있거든
Let me tell you some things
I learned working here.
첫째, 손님은 왕이다
First, the customer is always right.
미소는 놀라운 힘을 발휘한다
A smile goes a long way.
무례한 손님이 있다면?
머핀에 재채기를 해버려
And if anyone is ever rude to you,
sneeze muffin.
Thanks, Rach.
고맙다, 레이첼
너흰 정말 좋은 애들이야
Hey, look, you guys are just terrific,
you know?
이제 다들 나가라
손님 좀 받게
How about clearing out
so I can get some new customers?
물갈이 좀 하자
It's all about turnover.
조이
내 커피 안 갖다줄래?
Seriously, can I get my coffee?
미안하다, 로스
당장 대령할게
I'm sorry. I'll get it right now.
기다리게 했으니까
머핀도 하나 줄게
And since you waited,
I'll toss in a free muffin.
피비, 잠깐 얘기 좀 할래?
Phoebe, we'd like to talk to you.
좋아
Okay.
내가 결벽증일 수도 있고
레이첼이 호구일 수도 있어
So, maybe I am
a little high maintenance.
And maybe Rachel is
a little bit of a pushover.
그럼 넌 뭔 줄 알아?
But you know what you are?
이런 말은 미안하지만
피비 넌 별종이야
We are sorry to tell you this,
but you, Phoebe, are flaky.
하!
맞아, 나 별종이야
That's true, I am flaky.
별종이라도 괜찮다는 거야?
So, what, you're just okay
with being flaky?
그럼, 당연하지
Yeah, totally.
그렇다면 결벽증도 좋아
Then I'm okay
with being high maintenance.
그래, 난 호구라도 괜찮아
Yeah. And I am okay
with being a pushover.
멋지다, 잘 생각했어
That's great. Good for you guys.
난 결벽증 아냐!
-I am not high maintenance!
-I am not a pushover!
나도 호구 아냐!
-Who said you were?
-You did!
누가 그런 말을 해?
네가 그랬잖아
I'm flaky. I'll say anything.
난 별종이야
무슨 말을 못해
저기, 건터
Hey, Gunther.
Can you cover for me?
I got an audition.
자리 좀 비워도 될까요?
오디션 약속이 생겨서
나도 염색하러 가야 돼
No, I'm leaving to get my hair dyed.
지금 생머리가 더 좋은데
I like your natural color.
정말 괜찮은 배역이에요
한번 볼래요?
It's a great part.
I'm the lead guy's best friend.
난 주연의 제일 친한 친구고
바에서 그 친구 자릴 지키죠
I wait for him and save his seat.
Listen.
들어봐요
"I'm sorry, that seat's saved."
'미안한데 임자 있는 자리요'
-That's the whole part?
-Maybe he's not his best friend.
그게 다야?
제일 친한 친구는
아닌지 모르지만...
I'll see you.
한 시간 있다 보세
Oh, man.
I could totally get that part.
"I'm sorry, this seat is taken."
꼭 따낼 수 있었는데
'미안한데 임자 있는 자리요'
-Excuse me.
-No, I didn't mean you.
아, 죄송합니다
아뇨, 손님이 아니라...
But you believed me?
제 말이 그럴 듯한 가요?
방금 임자 있는 자리라면서요
I believed you were saving this seat
for someone.
So you'd hire me, right?
그럼 절 쓰시겠어요?
For what?
어디다가요?
바로 그거예요, 좋아요
Exactly!
All right, everybody listen up!
여러분, 주목하세요
한 시간만 문 닫겠습니다
The coffeehouse will be closed
for about an hour.
What?
뭐요?
청소년 보호차원입니다
It's for the kids.
마약으로부터 청소년을 보호하자
Yeah, to keep the kids off drugs.
It's a very important issue
in this month's Playboy.
이번 달 플레이보이에 실린
특집기사인데 다들 읽으셨죠?
I'm sure you all read about it.
또 오세요
Hey! Don't you wanna keep guns
away from kids?
이봐요, 총으로부터
청소년을 보호하자고요
-You said, "drugs."
-It's a vicious cycle. Get out!
마약이라고 했잖소
악순환의 고리예요
빨리 나가쇼
Go!
가!
-It's my joke.
- 내 조크였어
- 내 조크야
It's my joke.
- 내 조크라니까
- 내 조크래두
I don't think we're gonna settle this.
둘이선 해결 못 보겠다
맞아, 모니카한테 맡기자
Let's have Monica decide.
- 좋아
- 그래
-Hey, Mon!
-Get out here!
- 야, 모니카
- 잠깐 나와 봐
모니카
-Monica?
-Okay.
좋아
이게 누구 조크인지
자기가 결정을 내려 줘
You have to decide whose joke this is.
왜 나더러 결정하래?
Why do I have to?
공정한 사람은 자기밖에 없어
You're the only one that can be fair.
연인 사이에 어떻게
공정할 수가 있어
I can't be. You're my boyfriend.
하지만 난 오빠야
가족이라고
But I'm your brother. We're family.
세상에서 그보다 중요한 건 없지
That's the most important thing
in the world.
Don't try to sway her.
수 쓰지 마
I'm your only chance to have a baby.
자기 임신시킬 사람이 누구겠어?
자, 시작하자
-Okay, let's go.
-All right.
좋아, 우리가 각자 조크를
어떻게 생각해냈는지 말하면
We'll each tell you
how we came up with the joke...
넌 누구 얘기가 진실인지
가려내는 거야, 나겠지만
then you decide which one of us
is telling the truth. Me.
Chandler, you first.
챈들러 먼저
좋아, 두 달 전에 스티브랑
점심 먹다 생각난 조크거든
I thought of the joke two months ago
at lunch with Steve.
크리스마스에 만났던 사람?
-Did I meet him at Christmas?
-Can I finish?
끝까지 들을래?
여기서 탈락할래?
You want me to pick you?
봐, 난 너한테 이렇게
딱딱거리지 않아
See, I would never
snap at you like that.
(애기가 둘)
Two babies.
-Continue.
-Okay.
- 계속해
- 알았어
그때 스티브가 병원에 다녔는데
주치의가 멈피 박사였어
Steve said he had to go to the doctor.
And his doctor's name is Dr. Mompey.
내가 그랬지
'몽키 박사?'
I said, "Dr. Monkey?" And that is how
the whole Dr. Monkey thing came up.
이렇게 몽키 박사 얘기가
탄생된 거지
가소롭기 짝이 없구만
Are you kidding?
Okay, look, I study evolution.
들어봐, 난 진화론을
공부한 사람이야
Remember? Evolution.
진화론이 뭔지는 알지?
원숭이와 사람의 관계
Monkey into man.
Plus, I'm a doctor. And...
게다가 난 박사야
한때 원숭이도 키워봤고
I had a monkey.
내가 몽키 박사잖아!
I'm Dr. Monkey!
그 부분은 동감이다
I'm not arguing with that.
좋아, 이제 충분해
결정 내렸어
I've heard enough for my decision.
- 그래, 뭔데?
- 어서 들어보자
-Okay, so what..?
-Do tell.
You are both idiots.
두 사람 다 바보야
그 조크는 재미도 없고
여성을 비하하는 내용이야
It's not funny.
And it's offensive to women.
And doctors. And monkeys.
박사랑 원숭이들까지
저작권을 주장하고 싶어?
You shouldn't argue
over who gets credit.
끔찍한 조크를 세상에 퍼뜨린
파렴치한으로 지목해줄까?
You should argue over who gets blamed
for inflicting this joke on the world.
Now, let it go.
그만들 해둬
그 조크 엿 같으니까
The joke sucks.
- 네 조크다
- 천만에
-It's your joke.
-It is not.
-Oh, my God, Chandler, there you are.
-Hi.
어머, 챈들러
여기 있었네?
그래, 어서 와
저런, 피비랑 레이첼까지?
Hey, it's Phoebe and Rachel.
나 결벽증 아니라던 그 얘기
여기서 다시 한 번 해볼래?
Why don't you tell them...
what you told me about me
not being high maintenance.
모니카는 착실하고
자립심 강한 여성이야
Monica is a self-sufficient,
together lady.
함께 있으면 마치
휴양지에 온 것 같아
Being with her
has been like being on a vacation.
결벽증으로 보이는 건
사려 깊고 섬세한 성격
And what may be perceived
as high maintenance...
is merely attention to detail...
and...
그리고...
고결한 품성 때문이겠지
generosity of spirit.
와우! 이런 사기성 연설은
머리털 나고 처음 들어본다
Wow. You know what? That is the best
fake speech I think I've ever heard.
그래? 난 더한 것도 들어봤어
Really? I've heard better.
잠깐, 내가 시킨 거 아냐
Wait, he came up with that himself.
Tell them.
계속해봐, 챈들러
할말이 바닥났는데
그거 다시 할까?
I'm out of words.
Should I say it again?
난 결벽증이 절대
아니라니까, 챈들러
Look, I am not high maintenance!
I am not. Chandler!
You're a little high maintenance.
조금은 결벽증이야
You are on my list!
너 내 리스트에 올라갔어
Look, I'm sorry, but you're not..
미안해, 사실 자기가 편한
사람은 아니지만 열정적이야
You're not easygoing,
but you're passionate.
그건 좋은 점이지
And that's good.
사소한 일에 화를 내도
내가 있으니까
And when you get upset about little
things, I think I'm pretty good...
at making you feel better.
그걸 풀어줄 수 있잖아
난 그것도 좋아
That's good too.
They say you're high maintenance...
쟤들이 결벽증이라 해도 괜찮아
왜냐면 난 자길...
but it's okay, because I like...
maintaining you.
달래주는 게 좋으니까
이건 진짜 안 시켰어
I didn't tell him that.
그래야지
- 리스트에서 빼줄게
- 나 빠졌단다
-You're off my list.
-I'm off the list.
피비
Phoebe?
네 여자친구 못 돼도 상관없어
It's okay that you don't want me
to be your girlfriend.
이렇게 멋진
남자친구가 있으니까
I have the best boyfriend.
You know,
suddenly I find you very attractive.
어라?
갑자기 네가 너무 매력적이다
너 왔구나
오디션은 어땠어?
How'd the audition go?
망했다, 보기 좋게 떨어졌어
Oh, not good. No.
I didn't get the part.
And I lost my job here, so...
여기 일자리까지 잃었고
오디션 진짜 잘못 갔네
Wow, that is a bad audition.
어쩌다 여기서 짤렸어?
Well, how did you lose your job here?
난 오디션이 있었는데
I had the audition...
건터가 염색하러 간다고
가게를 지키고 있으라잖아
but Gunther said I had to stay
so he could get his hair dyed.
거기 다녀왔더니 짤랐더라
So I went anyway, and he fired me.
He left work
to do a personal errand...
주인이 사적인 용무로
대낮에 자릴 비우면서
and left you in charge
when you've been here two days?
이틀밖에 안 된 너한테
가게를 맡겼다고?
That's not right.
그건 경우가 아니지
What are you gonna do?
내가 무슨 힘이 있나?
그냥 넘어갈 일이 아냐
You can't let him get away with that.
아무래도 안 되겠다
한 마디 해야지...
I won't let him get away with that.
I'm gonna say..
가만있는 게 나을까?
I shouldn't say anything.
No, I should say something!
그래도 얘기해야겠어
건터
Gunther?
I want you to give Joey his job back.
조이 일자리 돌려줘요
이건 옳지 않아요
-It's not fair that you have to fire..
-Okay.
- 그런 일로...
- 알았어
네?
-What?
-He can have his job back.
다시 일 시킨다고
That's right,
he can have his job back.
그러는 게 마땅한 처사죠
알아들었다니 다행이군요
Glad we got that all straightened out.
됐다, 조이
There you go, Joey.
다시 일하란다
-Got your job back.
-That's great. Thanks.
잘됐다, 정말 고마워
그럼, 나 괜찮았지?
누구한테 호구래?
Pretty nice, huh?
Now who's a pushover?
-Rach, you're in my seat.
-I'm sorry.
- 거기 내 자리야
- 미안
그럼 너희는 누굴
여자친구 삼고 싶은데?
I never heard who you'd pick
to be your girlfriend.
-I'd pick you, Phoebe.
-Yeah, definitely you, Phoebe.
난 너야, 피비
그래, 당연히 너지
Yeah, I kind of thought.
그럴 줄 알았다
-Never.
-It would totally be you.
- 얘들아
- 그래, 하나 물어보자
If you had to pick one
of the other two to go out with...
너희들 중 아무나 한 사람을
사귄다면 누굴 선택하겠니?
who would you pick?
-No way.
-I'm not answering.
- 말도 안 돼
- 대답할 가치도 없다
조이
Joey.
No way, I'm not answering that.
말도 안 돼
대답할 가치도 없다